# Mohd Shahid

New Delhi



mohd47149@gmail.com



9717201964



linkedin.com/in/mohd-shahid-715978210

## Summary

Experienced Mathematics Subject Matter Expert and Quality Content Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the education management industry. Skilled in Lesson Planning, Educational Technology, Instructional Design, Curriculum Development, and Teacher Training. Strong media and communication professional with a BCA - Bachelor of Computer Applicalition focused in Mathematics from Indra Gandhi Open University.

## **Experience**

## Information Technology Teacher

Arth Institute Of Computer Education

Sep 2022 - Present (7 months)

- · Basic Computer Course Provide
- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- PHP
- Ps 2023
- Illustration 2022
- Corel Draw 2021

## Subject Matter Expert

Digituala

Dec 2021 - Dec 2022 (1 year 1 month)

- Solution Provide for K-12 Mathematics.
- · Worked on Brainly Portal.
- · US, UK based project.

## **66** Translator Expert

ConveGenius

Apr 2022 - Oct 2022 (7 months)

- · English to Hindi Translation.
- Translation of Mathematics Questions.
- QC of Translations.
- · Work on CMS.
- Inhouse Work.

## SME-Mathemetics

Rafiki Solutions Pvt. Ltd. - The Knowledge Crafter

Aug 2022 - Sep 2022 (2 months)

· Solution Provide on Brainly Portal

· US based Project

#### TRIVIUM SME

**Trivium Education** 

Mar 2022 - Jun 2022 (4 months)

- Solution Provide for K-12 Physics
- · Worked on Study Smarter Portal

### **Subject Matter Expert**

**Trivium Education** 

Oct 2021 - Mar 2022 (6 months)

- Solution Provide for K-16 Mathematics
- Worked on StudySmarter Portal

## **Subject Matter Expert**

**Trivium Education** 

Mar 2021 - Sep 2021 (7 months)

- Solution Provide for K-12 Mathematics
- · Worked on Brainly Portal
- · US, UK based project

## **Subject Matter Expert**

**Trivium Education** 

Feb 2021 - Apr 2021 (3 months)

· Solution Provide on Brainly Portal

#### **Education**



## (S) Indira Gandhi National Open University

Bachelor's degree, BCA (Maths)

Jul 2021 - Present



#### **SBV No.1 Molarband**

Mar 2019 - Mar 2021



#### Govt. Boys Sr. Sec. School

Mar 2014 - Mar 2019

#### Skills

Teamwork • Adobe Photoshop • CorelDRAW • Adobe Illustrator • HTML5 • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • JavaScript • PHP • MSQL • Web Design